

FRONTEND ENGINEER

CONTACT

Phone Q 💆 🔽





+375 29 624-83-77

Email @



andrey.voronin.work@gmail.com

LinkedIn in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andr ey-voronin

LANGUAGES

English ___

B1 - Intermediate

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

 JavaScript (ES5, ES6, ES7), HTML/CSS (BEM), LESS/SASS/SCSS, TypeScript

Experienced

CMS, Frameworks, Libraries:

· Angular, NgRx, RxJs, Material UI/CDK, JQuery, Kendo UI

Experienced

 React/Redux/MobX/MUI, Node, Gulp, Webpack, Bootstrap

Experienced

Vue, PHP, Wordpress, d3.js

Novice

ABOUT ME

Creative frontend developer with 3+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine existing background with strong technical skills to excel as a Frontend Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11.2022-Present.

Axamit

Frontend Engineer

- Development product architecture and algoritm.
- UI design and interface creation.
- Adaptive and cross-browser application layout based on design layouts.
- · Setting up functionality (buttons, sliders, forms, galleries and other elements) and writting scripts.
- · Checking and testing functionality.
- Refactoring, improving, optimizing the code and speeding up applications.
- Active interaction with backend developers and other team members in the Agile format.
- Estimations.
- · Demo with customers.
- Developing autotests and fixing bugs.
- · Code review.

09.2020-11.2022

HiQo Solutions

Frontend Engineer

- Development product architecture and algoritm.
- UI design and interface creation.
- Adaptive and cross-browser application layout based on design layouts.
- Setting up functionality (buttons, sliders, forms, galleries and other elements) and writting scripts.
- · Checking and testing functionality.

Version Control Systems:

· GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab

Experienced

API Testing:

Postman

Experienced

Tools:

· Devtools, Swagger

Experienced

Database:

Firebase/Firestore

Experienced

MS SQL Server

Novice

Work tracking systems:

Jira

Experienced

RECOMMENDATIONS

Timofey Ivanov,

HiQo Solutions, Senior BA/PL https://www.linkedin.com/in/ timofey-ivanov 06.2020-09.2020

HiQo Solutions

Frontend Trainee (Internship)

- Development of an application similar to Trello using the Angular framework and Material UI library.
- Checking and testing functionality.
- Interaction with team members.
- Adaptive and cross-browser landing page layout based on design layout.
- Estimations

COURSES

2019 IT Academy

Website development with HTML, CSS, & JavaScript

2020 IT Academy

Web application development with JavaScript

EDUCATION

2005 **Belorussian National Technical University:** International Economic Relations

ADDITIONAL INFO

IT Academy Certificates